minecraftshop.com 2019-10-22

# Official Minecraft Store – Powered by J!NX : Privacy Policy

* * *

### What information does J!NX collect?

We collect the following types of personally identifiable information: your contact information (such as name, postal or email address, or phone number), name and email address of gift card recipients, username and password, payment information such as PayPal or credit card details, shipping information (including the shipping address and phone number), purchase history at our Sites, and photographs or other media that you submit on our Sites or through our social media channels. Also, by submitting a photograph or other media, you give Jinx a non-exclusive, perpetual, sublicensable, world-wide, permanent license to use it subject to a subsequent deletion/change request. You also represent and warrant that you hold all rights necessary to post such photograph or other media and agree to defend and indemnify Jinx in the event it results in a third party asserts a claim against Jinx. 

Upon checkout, you will be asked if you would like to be included in our mailing list for product updates. This is not required and if you do NOT check this box, the denial is honored. If you choose NOT to be included, you will not receive newsletters or mass email from us. If you do choose to be added to our mailing list, either via ordering or the subscribe box in the sidebar, you can easily unsubscribe by following the instructions at the bottom of our newsletter.

### What information do parties other than J!NX collect?

To better understand how our visitors use our service and to help us provide a better experience, we may collect and store information either directly in log files and cookies, or via third party vendors, including Google, Facebook, that use web tracking technologies, including cookies and web beacons. This information may include pages that you have visited, your IP address, browser type and your operating system. 

### What are "cookies" and how do we use them?

J!NX uses cookies to track your current shopping cart. Cookies are small bits of data that are sent to your browser and stored on your hard drive. We require that cookies have been turned on (in your browser) in order to use this site.

### What do we do with the information we collect?

We use it to ship your order. That's it.

### How long does Jinx keep my data?

Personal data that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes. Outside of shipping data, personally identifiable information will be pseudonymized after two years.

### With whom do we share your information and for what purpose?

We contract with other companies to provide certain services, such as email distribution; shipping; name and address verification; market research; and payment processing. These service providers are not authorized to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements. 

We may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, or when required by law to do so. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection, legal compliance or investigations. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes. 

### Contact possibility via the website

The website of JINX contains information that enables a quick electronic contact to our customer service. If you contact us by e-mail or via a contact form, the personal data transmitted by is automatically stored. Such personal data transmitted on a voluntary basis by you to us is stored for the purpose of contacting you. There is no transfer of this personal data to third parties. 

### What if I want to change my account information or see what data you have?

Updating Your Profile. You may update or correct your personally identifiable information related to your account directly on the site or by contacting Customer Support at support@jinx.com. If you wish to request deletion of your personal information, then please contact us at support@jinx.com. We will respond requests within a reasonable timeframe. We retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, contractual statute of limitations, resolution of disputes, and enforcement of our agreements. Please note that we may not be able to delete data upon request depending on the reasons above and the nature of your interactions (e.g., we retain data to notify customers of product recalls). 

If you wish to see what data we have for you, email support@jinx.com. 

Gift Card Recipients. Your gift card recipient may contact us at support@jinx.com to request an update, correction or deletion of their personally information. Again, for various reasons stated above, we may not be able to delete information upon request. 

### Your consent

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by J!NX.com as outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

JINX does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use jinx.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 without the consent of the child's parent or guardian. 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may change our Privacy Policy. We will post those changes on this page so that our customers will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we share the information with others.

_This version of the J!NX Privacy Policy is effective May 22, 2018._
